Contact

barzi.mozhdeh@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/barzi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Experience Design (UED)
Information Architecture
User-centered Design

Languages

Persian (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional) Russian (Elementary) Japanese (Limited Working)

Certifications

Google UX Design

Honors-Awards

Singapore Management University Innovation Award (SMUIA)

Patents

Instant simultaneous messaging

Mozhdeh Barzi

UX Designer | Specialty in Information Architecture Tokyo

Summary

My journey to UX design has not been the most straightforward, but it has been fulfilling.

Being an empathetic and active listener helped me to find a comprehensive yet agile approach to solve real life challenges/problems, which led me to UX design field.

+5 years experience as a UX generalist focusing on human-centered design process to produce a user-focused MVP.

Expert-level proficiency with major designing tools such as Figma, Adobe XD, Sketch, Adobe Photoshop and illustrator.

Founding member of the ShootShot mobile app which was designed and developed based on a patented algorithm to eliminate friendliness bias in communications.

Experience

Chatify App Co-founder & Product Designer February 2020 - Present (2 years 3 months) Tokyo, Japan

Avanti Staffing Interpreter March 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 1 month) Tokyo, Japan

ShootShot シュートショット User Researcher & Product Designer October 2018 - February 2019 (5 months) Tokyo, Japan

Moscow School of Management SKOLKOVO Communication Expert

2014 - 2015 (1 year)

Moscow, Russia

SMU Institute of Innovation & Entrepreneurship Concept Designer JaaPaa July 2013 - December 2013 (6 months) Singapore

Education

TCJ Japanese Language School

· (March 2017 - March 2018)

Shiraz University

Master's degree, Applied Linguistics, history of visual communication \cdot (2010 - 2012)

Kuwait University

Bachelor's degree, Art/Art Studies, General · (2006 - 2010)